

## **PROFILE**

Hello, I am ISHAL, Programmer with 12+ years of experience using PHP, Laravel, Java Mobile, Flutter to develop, test and observe applications that have been created. Have designed and developed more than 30 apps. Looking for new experiences to gain additional knowledge. I am not a hypocrite so that's why I also want to earn more money so that I can help others in the future.

I hope to be given the opportunity to work. I like remote using git.

## CONTACT

PHONE: 0822-7153-3622

WEBSITE:

https://saluonecity.github.io/portofolio-reactis/index.html

EMAIL:

saluonecity@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Reading AL-QUR'AN Mountain Climbing Coding

# RIDSAL LANTA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

### **EDUCATION**

#### STMIK DIPANEGARA MAKASSAR

[2004 - 2011]

[Bachelor of Information Systems]

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Banggai Class II Immigration Office [ PHP / Java Mobile ] 2016-2022

- Creating queuing applications (PHP/MySQL) and client server installations
- Create a foreign worker data search application using android studio (Java/SQLite)
- Debugged and implemented new solutions for queuing application and foreign worker data search application

# Office of the Civil Service Agency [Laravel / API / Flutter] 2022 – Now

 Design, test and develop training applications for PPPK and attendance applications using the Laravel API / MySQL Backend and Flutter Frontend.

## CV. Teknologi Anak Nusantara [Full Stack Developer] 2012 – Now

- 2012 NOW
- Design, test and develop various bespoke applications.
- Monitor the process of running the application and fix if there are errors

#### **FAVORITE SKILLS**

- Laravel
- Node js
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Linux
- React (JavaScript, TypeScript)
- Java Mobile (Android Studio)
- Flutter / Dart Github